howtogermany.com 2019-03-30

# How To Germany - Privacy Policy

You may give us personal information about you, such as your name and/or email address. This privacy policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

## How and where personal information is collected:

  * through an opt-in newsletter subscription
  * through an opt-in digital issue update request
  * through emails sent to us
  * through third party enquiry forms on certain pages of the website

## How your personal information is used:

How To Germany does not share personal information directly sent to us with third parties.

On some pages of the website there are third party enquiry forms. They are provided so that a reader can contact a company directly to request price quotes or other information. The companies that provide those forms collect information given in third party enquiry forms. You should be aware that the information you supply in those forms is going to that company. The companies are clearly identified.

How To Germany has the necessary Security Certificates to ensure that transmission of information to and from us is safe and secure. Any companies with an enquiry form on the website are also required to have the necessary Security Certificates before they are allowed to put the form on the website.

How To Germany is not responsible for the republishing of the content found on this website on other websites or in other media without permission.

The information you give us is absolutely safe with us. We will never rent, sell, share or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties. If you subscribe to our newsletter or digital issue update request, you can unsubscribe easily at any time.

If you sent us an email inquiring about advertising on the website or offering to make editorial contributions, we may contact you from time to time regarding those subjects. You may opt out from receiving any information from us at any time and ask us to remove your personal/contact information from our database.

## Cookie Policy

### What are cookies?

A cookie is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit a website.

In addition to our own cookies, we also use various third parties cookies to report usage statistics of the website.

How To Germany uses cookies for the following purposes: to enable certain website functions, to provide analytics, to store your preferences and to analyze content performance. We also include the occasional cookie on behalf of advertisers to help them market their products or services.

Cookies are not used to collect personal information. Cookies can be deleted at anytime by modifying your Internet browser’s settings. The cookie-related information is not used to identify you personally. These cookies are not used for any purpose other than those described here.

### What are your choices regarding cookies?

Enabling cookies is not strictly necessary for the website to work but it will provide you with a better browsing experience. You can delete or block these cookies, but if you do that some features of this site may not work as intended.

If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages or preferences section of your web browser.

### Where can you find more information about cookies?

You can learn more about cookies and the following third party website:  
AllAboutCookies: <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>
